Andrew Popp

4840 Skyline Dr, KS, 66205 (314) 347-5558

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrewpopp123/ | GitHub: https://github.com/APopp524 |

Portfolio: https://apopp524.github.io/Responsive-Portfolio/

Summary

Full Stack web developer with a Digital Media Production degree and experience in the live events, media, and television industry. Recently earned a certificate in Full Stack development from the University of Kansas with new skills in Javascript, jQuery, CSS3, HTML5, Bootstrap and responsive web design. I enjoy problem solving and am a flexible worker that can work as a team or individually to get the task completed. I strive to further my knowledge and challenge myself everyday.

Technical Skills

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, GIT, GitHub, Adobe Creative Suite

Experience

May 2018 - March 2020

Harvest Productions, North Kansas City, MO - Lead Video Technician

- Lead video for live event productions such as conferences, expos, concerts, sporting events, and shows.
- Communicated with clients for Audio and Visual troubleshooting, maintenance, and content creation.

April 2019 - January 2020

Major League Baseball, Kansas City, MO - Data Operations

- Video Room Monitor for home and away teams during Royals games at Kauffman Stadium.
- Statistical tracking during Royals games.

January 2016 - January 2018

KMOS-TV, Warrensburg, MO - Producer

- Television studio production, filming, and editing for shows Pause, Show-Me Ag, Lowdown
- Live television filming and replay for University of Central Missouri sporting events.

Education

University of Kansas, Lawrence, KS

University of Kansas BootCamp - Full Stack Web Development

An intensive 6 month long boot camp dedicated to designing and building web applications. Skills learned consisted of HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Node.js

University of Central Missouri, Warrensburg, MO

Bachelor of Science - Digital Media Production degree

Graduated May 2018 with a minor in Sports Communication and specialized coursework in Video & Audio Production, Media Promotions, Digital Video Editing, HTML & CSS Basics